[Music]
we all know the benefits of living a
healthy and active lifestyle it can
combat stress reduce anxiety build
confidence and increase our energy but
did you know there's another way to
benefit from making healthy choices
Manulife vitality is an innovative form
of life insurance that was built with
your health in mind as a vitality member
you can earn rewards by doing things as
simple as going to the dentist getting
your flu shot or going for a walk by
focusing on your health and staying
active you can save on your next
vacation receive gift cards decrease
your cost of insurance and even earn a
free Apple watch I'm a vitality member
and have personally enjoyed the benefits
of this program it has helped me
establish healthy habits while earning
rewards and saving on my insurance
why just buy life insurance when you can
be rewarding
[Music]